macheesmo.com 2010-05-29

# Privacy Policy | Macheesmo

**Privacy Policy for Macheesmo.com  
**_Updated 03/2010_

The privacy of my visitors to macheesmo.com is important to me.

At Macheesmo.com, I recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information I receive and collect when you use and visit Macheesmo.com, and how I safeguard your information.  I never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, Macheesmo collects and use the data contained in log files.  The information in the log files include  your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit the site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout the site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
Macheesmo does use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit the site.  This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

There are also third party advertisements on Macheesmo.com to support the site.  Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on the site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.  This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings for Macheesmo, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.  However, this can affect how you are able to interact with the site as well as other websites.  This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
